Here is Prophet T.B. Joshua praying for the people in the name of Jesus Christ.
He encounters this lady and the power of God exposes whatever that is not of God in her life.
Let's see how she was delivered.
I want blood.
Speak out!
You want what?
Blood!
You want blood?
What have you done to her?
I want to kill.
What have you done to her career and her family?
Speak!
I split.
Speak loud, you demon!
You split the family?
I split.
How many are you in this body?
Eleven.
Who is number one?
Number one!
Death.
Number two?
Spirit of what?
Speak out!
Look at this man. Who is this man to you?
She married him.
She married him?
Who are you in this body?
A man.
You are a man?
What can you say about your wife?
She is my wife; she has been struggling.
She has been afflicted for quite a while.
Who is the cause of the troubles in the marriage?
Speak out!
Who is the cause of their troubles?
I am.
You are the cause?
How long have you been in her?
Since birth.
How did you enter her?
In a dream.
In a dream?
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Prophet T.B. Joshua offers spirit-filled prayer to her,
and the evil spirit flees at the mention of the name Jesus Christ.
Glory be to God!
She is free in Jesus' name.
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Emmanuel!
(God with us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Danielle Amy and I am from Australia.
The man beside me is my lovely husband Trevor.
You are both very welcome.
All the way from Australia - you've really come a long way.
The Holy Spirit is the rewarder.
You have been delivered as we saw on the screen.
We want to hear from you about how those evil spirits have been affecting your life.
Please, go ahead with your testimony.
What brought me to The SCOAN was that
I had been struggling with my health and had been diagnosed
with several autoimmune diseases and disorders.
My family members are quite sick and I was looking at them.
I just believed that God had more for myself and my family
and I wasn't going to take "no" for an answer.
We applied to come to The SCOAN and to receive healing and deliverance.
Our sister mentioned that she came not only due to the evil attacks she was facing
but also because she had some eating disorders and allergies that had been affecting her life.
Please go ahead and let us know how these problems had affected you.
Autoimmune is when the body attacks itself.
I was constantly being diagnosed with different problems within my body
because my body kept on attacking different areas.
It was just exhausting.
I would spend the majority of my time by myself or in bed because I was just beyond exhausted.
The Lord has healed me.
Since the deliverance and healing, I haven't taken any of the medications that I usually take on a daily basis.
I feel a lot better, I have a lot more of energy.
Let's put our hands for Jesus!
You mentioned that you were having some different health-wise problems
but it was as a result of the evil attacks you had been facing.
You mentioned that you went to the doctors and they kept diagnosing different problems with you.
Can you explain more about the evil attacks you experienced and how they affected you?
I had been having evil attacks.
The first one that I remember was when I was about five or six years of age.
I've been having them throughout my entire life - either in dreams or visions but often in the physical.
Sometimes, I would just wake up from my sleep and I would have bruises and strangle marks around my neck.
I would have bites on my body in places that I wouldn't be able to reach by myself.
I would have bruises and scratches all over me.
I would have evil spirits come and visit me and speak to me when I was awake like I am now.
OK. You mentioned that when you woke up, you would physically see bruises and scratches on your body
in places that you couldn't reach yourself,
letting you know that something else had been doing these things to you.
Yes, that's correct.
Did you ever explain these things to the doctors in Australia?
No.
I actually felt quite ashamed and isolated.
There are very few people that I would actually share this with
because I guess culturally, it's very different in Australia.
If I ever told the doctor how I got the bruises or some of the injuries I'd sustained,
which actually led to me being hospitalized,
I was afraid that I would be institutionalized because they would think I was insane.
Did you explain these things to your husband?
Yes, I did but he began to encounter them for himself.
He was a witness after we got married.
You mentioned that you would also see them physically, not just in the dream.
Can you give us an instance of when this happened to you?
I had one night just after we got married.
I wasn't able to sleep so I went into another room to lay down.
I fell asleep and I had a dream.
There were three beings standing in my room and they were talking about how I was going to die.
I was going to be involved in a car accident but it wasn't the car accident that was going to kill me -
it was a ruptured artery that was going to kill me.
I woke up from the dream because I heard talking, and I physically saw the three beings standing before me.
Can you describe what you saw standing before you?
They were tall and dark in appearance.
I saw like a shimmering green as if they had green coats or capes on, although it was very dark in the room.
The room was very cold.
I just felt...
Any way to describe it - it is just death.
Danielle Amy & Husband - Deliverance Testimony
I called my husband.
He came in and commented that there was something wrong, before I even said to him what had happened.
We began to pray.
We both got up and went into our dining area.
We had a big book case.
On top of the book case were several candles.
One of the candles had been taken down and put on the kitchen bench.
A green flame was burning in the candle.
Neither my husband or I had touched the candle.
Neither of us had brought it down or lit the flame.
We felt such an evil presence in the house.
You mentioned just before that the three beings were standing there
and you heard them discussing a plan of how to kill you
but your husband walked in and said something was not right.
Did he see the beings as well at that time?
No, he didn't.
After praying together, we went back to bed together.
I was laying awake.
My husband fell asleep.
While I was lying there, this being came over me and began to scream violently in my face.
My husband woke up from his sleep, rebuking in Jesus' name.
He turned to me describing what he had just seen, what had just happened in his dream.
What he had seen in his dream was exactly what I had witnessed being awake as I was laying.
What you experienced physically; a demon shouting over your head -
your husband saw it happening too, as he was sleeping but he woke up rebuking this demon in Jesus' name?
Yes, that is correct.
What happened after that?
At that time I wasn't working because I was quite unwell.
I had a friend that was also unwell and I wanted to cook for her and her family.
I made food and put it in the car to go.
As I was driving, I went to turn down the street to her house.
Out of nowhere, a car came and hit me and totaled the car that I was in.
I hit my head and hurt my neck but I didn't want to go to hospital so I just went home.
My husband came home to be with me.
As I was laying on the couch, because I was in quite a bit of pain,
a sort of a tiger came and bit me on the neck.
I was in excruciating pain and I couldn't move.
My heart was not beating properly and I had pain down my arms.
I was admitted into hospital, into emergency.
OK, sorry...
We just want to get some thing clear from you.
You mentioned that after having that strange encounter that day,
listening to evil beings explaining how they planned to kill you in a car crash,
the very same day, as you were in your car on your way to drop some food to a sick friend,
you had a car accident.
Then you went home and you said a tiger came in and bit your neck.
Were you sleeping that time when you saw a tiger coming in or was it physically?
Yes, that was physically.
I hadn't been asleep.
Yes.
The only way to describe it is like when you have a fire and there is smoke -
it was the same density and texture but very clear and there were colours.
It came and bit me.
So, the tiger physically came into where you were?
Yes, it did.
What happened after you went to the hospital?
I was admitted for five days in intensive care.
They weren't able to find out what the problem was.
I was in such a bad pain I couldn't get out of the bed to go to the bathroom, or anything.
They couldn't relieve the pain so they accidentally knocked me with too much pain relievers.
I ended up going catatonic and unresponsive for a period.
Just before that happened, whilst receiving one of the injections,
again, I saw the tiger come and bite me.
Eventually, they ended up doing an MRI scan.
They found that the muscles around my artery and neck had been constricted.
They were concerned that it was going to cause a stroke.
They couldn't work out what was causing it.
The doctors couldn't understand what was happening to you.
You mentioned that they gave you so much medication that your whole body became unresponsive
and you were in a critical condition.
Yes, that's correct.
At first I was showing no signs at all that the medication was affecting me negatively or positively.
There was a "build up" in my system and it ended up just hitting me in one go.
So, at this point you realized that your problem had gone beyond human solution, beyond physical means?
Yes.
I knew that it was spiritual.
I'd known all my life that it was spiritual.
I became desperate for a breakthrough.
I believed that God heals, delivers, and He is a good God.
We decided that we wanted to come to The SCOAN.
We made an application to come.
How did you find out about The SCOAN?
About a year after this attack, my husband and I were looking at some things on Youtube.
I don't think it was related but we ended up seeing a video pop-up.
At first we didn't want to click on it because we thought it might be evil
but we decided to click on it anyway and our lives were changed as a result.
So instantly, when you started watching videos from The SCOAN your life began to change?
Yes.
Our house was filled with peace.
Instead of feeling a demonic presence, we began to feel an angelic presence.
Glory be to God!
Let's put our hands for Jesus Christ!
We thank God for Emmanuel TV - one of the means He is using to change lives.
Finally, you and your husband came to The SCOAN for your deliverance.
Can you share with us what happened on the day when you received the prayer and the deliverance?
Watching the video is actually quite surreal.
I just got hit and it was on my slack and I was stunned.
I guess any way to describe it is like I was behind a pane of glass and a 3D movie was happening
around me but there was no interaction on my behalf.
I heard talking but it was like I was waiting to hear what someone else was saying.
There was a strange voice coming that I was hearing.
As you were receiving the deliverance you saw that there was a spiritual warfare going on at that time?
Yes, I did.
Now, you are delivered.
What are the differences that you have noticed in your life?
I am a lot more peaceful.
I haven't had any more evil attacks or spiritual visitations.
I have just got a lot more energy.
My body feels really good.
My appetite has got a lot better as well.
Glory be to God! Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
We want to hear a few words from your husband standing beside you,
what he would like to say about the experiences, what he noticed in your life previously and now
that you are delivered in Jesus' name.
Please go ahead, starting with your name and what you have to say
about what God has done in the life of your wife.
My name is Trevor Philips and I'm from Australia.
Just to testify to the goodness of God...
Prior to my wife's deliverance and encounter with the Father,
she was experiencing a lot of demonic, evil attacks, frustration, stress, serious health conditions
that medically could not be resolved.
Visits to different doctors just led to dead ends.
After her deliverance by the grace of God, she is full of peace, radiant, calm, relaxed.
She just seems overall like a different person.
Glory be to God.
Amen. Let's put our hands together!
That is the evidence of Jesus Christ: lives changed.
Madam, we'd love to hear from you once again.
We want to hear your words of advice for others
because we believe that many people have been going through a similar thing.
We believe you have some words of advice to encourage them.
My advice especially to people of the "Western world" is that the spiritual realm is a reality.
I believe that there are a lot of people who have suffered in similar ways as I did.
But Jesus has conquered the enemy.
Jesus has given us salvation.
He has delivered us and He has healed us.
I think it is important that we allow Him to save us, to heal us, to deliver us because He is more than capable.
He is total in His healing, His deliverance and His salvation.
There is no partiality about it.
He is amazing.
Amen! Let's clap for our Lord!
Danielle Amy & Husband - Deliverance Testimony
He is amazing indeed.
He has totally transformed the life of this lady.
You mentioned before that you had an eating disorder, some allergies,
you were taking a lot of medication as a result of this.
How about now?
How is your physical health?
I feel really good.
I have got a lot of energy, strength and stamina that I didn't have before.
My appetite has returned.
For the benefit of the viewers;
we also want to ask once again about the time when Prophet T.B. Joshua was praying for you
and the spiritual warfare was going on.
Can you explain how you felt at that time?
What happened to you at that time of deliverance?
It was like I was just removed, like I was in "echo" of something that was happening.
It was like me as a person was lagging behind whatever was going on, whatever warfare was happening.
Spiritually, it was like it all was one second delayed for me, and I was watching it after it had happened.
I guess the way to describe it is that my body felt stunned.
Actually, there was like a hand upon my head, upon my forehead for quite a while afterwards.
It was very soothing and comforting.
When the man of God delivered you, you fell to the ground.
How did you feel when you got up?
I felt a bit disoriented about what just happened but I felt really good and like "lighter".
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Let's put our hands together for Him!
Do you mean that today you are completely delivered and free?
I'm free.
Thank You, Jesus!
Thank you, Prophet T.B. Joshua, for allowing us to eat of the fruit of your life.
Amen.
"Thank you" is a response from a happy and free heart.
Let's put our hands together one more time!